https://www.pinehurst.com/privacy-policy/

The Pinehurst Promise. Learn More ›
MenuPlan Your StayBook OnlineMeetings & GroupsWeddingsShop#InPinehurst MenuGolfAccommodationsDiningSpaActivitiesPackagesMeetings & GroupsWeddingsShop#InPinehurst Menu
Privacy PolicyPINEHURST RESORT & COUNTRY CLUB ONLINE PRIVACY AND SECURITYEffective Date:  January 1, 2020At Pinehurst Resort & Country Club, we are committed to respecting your privacy.This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) explains how Pinehurst Resort & Country Club (“Pinehurst Resort,” “we,” “our,” or “us”) collect and use personal information and the choices you can make.  This Policy applies to your use of Pinehurst.com and our other general audience websites, applications and services that link to this Policy.  This Policy also addresses information we collect from you when you contact one of our customer service or sales representatives, or when you respond to a survey or enter a contest or sweepstakes that we administer.We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy in its entirety before using our services. By making a purchase or reservation, you acknowledge that you have read and agree to this Privacy Policy.What personal information do we collect? How do we use that information?Do we share your information with third parties?What options do you have to limit our collection and use of your personal information?How do we keep your information secure?How do we make updates to this policy?How can you contact us with questions about your privacy or this Policy?Supplemental Notice to California ResidentsWhat personal information do we collect? How do we use that information?We collect various types of personal information when you register via our websites, mobile sites or mobile applications (our “Sites and Apps”); purchase any products or services from us; book reservations, schedule tee times or appointments; visit one of our locations; contact one of our customer service or sales representatives; or complete a survey or enter a contest or sweepstakes that we sponsor. This information may be collected directly from you (for example, when you complete our forms or enter your information on our websites to make a purchase) or indirectly through your device or browser when you visit our Sites and Apps.We use your information to fulfill product orders, to customize and improve the advertising and content you see, to offer suggestions for personalized products based on your interests, to deliver marketing communications and promotional materials that you may be interested in, to contact you and provide customer service, to protect the security or integrity of our databases or websites, to detect and prevent fraud or illegal activity, to take precautions against liability, to detect and remediate violations of our Terms of Use or other misuse of our Sites and Apps, to develop and improve our products and services and for internal operational purposes.The following chart describes what categories of personal information we may collect, how we collect that information from you, and the business purposes for which we generally use such information:Information Type Source Purpose Third-Party Sharing Direct Identifiers (Customer Name, Postal Address, Phone Number, E-mail Address)Provided directly by customerMaintaining and servicing your accountProviding customer serviceProcessing and fulfilling your orders or reservationsProcessing paymentsAdvertising and marketing our services and products to youDetecting security incidents and protecting against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity Customer service providers Marketing and advertising servicesAppointment /reservation scheduling servicesSurveys, sweepstakes, and contestsPayment and chargeback processors Mailing and shipping servicesIdentity Verification Information (Government-issued ID, Driver License)Provided directly by customerIdentity verification as needed to protect against deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity NoneHousehold Information(Family Member names, date of birth and/or age)Provided directly by customer Maintaining and servicing your accountProcessing and fulfilling your orders or reservations
NoneUser-generated content (including photos) Provided directly by customer Providing customer serviceMarketing and advertising service providersPayment information (credit card information, only last four digits are stored)Provided directly by customerProcessing payments on your orders/reservationsDetecting security incidents and protecting against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activityCustomer service providersPayment and chargeback processorsFraud prevention and site securityPurchase information (purchase date, purchase totals, product types)Provided directly by customerProviding customer serviceProcessing payments on your orders/reservationsAnalytics to improve our products and servicesAdvertising and marketing our products and services to you Customer service providersPayment and chargeback processorsDigital Identifiers(IP Address, Cookies, Website Browsing and Interaction Activity, Other Device or Browser Identifiers)Collected indirectly from customer’s browser or deviceEnhancing your user experienceAnalytics to improve our products and servicesAdvertising and marketing our products to youDetecting security incidents and protecting against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activityMarketing and advertising service providersWebsite performance and analytics vendorsFraud prevention and site securityInferences about customer preferences and characteristicsInferred from information provided by customer and information collected indirectly from customer’s browser or deviceEnhancing your user experienceAnalytics to improve our products and servicesAdvertising and marketing our products to youMarketing and advertising service providers Website performance and analytics vendors In addition to any personal information that you might provide when you do things like buy our products and services, we may also have access to other information about you if you interact with our brand via social media.Social MediaIf you log into your account through a social media site, we will also have access to certain information from that site, such as your name, account information and profile photo, in accordance with the site’s account verification procedures. Also, if you interact with content on our social media profiles (for example, if you “like” or share a post from one of our brand’s Facebook, Twitter, or Instagram accounts), those social media sites may share information about you with us, including your public profile, e-mail address and friend list. If you choose to “like” or share content, information about you may be publicly displayed on the social network, depending on your privacy settings. You should review the privacy policy of that social media site and check your privacy settings through that site. If you post information on a social media or another third-party service that references our brand or our products and services (e.g., via a Twitter hashtag), we may publish your post on our social media accounts or websites.Information You Provide About OthersBefore you upload and/or share personal information of others through our service, please ensure that you have the consent of such persons to do so.CookiesWe and our service providers collect information about how you use our services – for example what web or mobile pages you have viewed – to analyze trends, generate analytics, provide a better user experience, improve our products and services, detect and prevent fraud or security incidents and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Our Sites and Apps use pixel tags, web beacons and similar tracking technologies (collectively referred to as “Cookies”) that are created when you use our online services and are stored on your computer or mobile device.Cookies help us offer convenient features like recognizing your browser when you visit, customizing your current and future visits, and providing you with information that interests you, and storing the contents of your shopping cart until you are ready to check out. We also use the information we collect to compile statistics about our visitors and their use of our site to monitor site traffic, develop marketing programs and improve our website design and content.We use the information collected by our third-party service providers using Cookies to analyze and track data, improve our services, determine the popularity of certain content, and better understand our users’ online activity. Our service providers may also show you advertisements for our products and services on other websites, and may combine this information with other information those service providers have gathered about your visits to those other websites so that the advertisements you receive are more likely to be of interest to you.Other SourcesWe may also obtain data that is publicly available or from third party sources, such as address verification services, to improve the accuracy of and add to what we know about our customers and prospective customers. We may combine this publicly available information with your personal information for the purposes described in this policy.Employment In addition to information collected from our customers, we and our service providers also collect certain information from candidates who apply for a job with Pinehurst Resort to contact you about your application and evaluate your qualifications for the position, including your name, phone number, e-mail address, postal address, education information and employment information.How do we share your information with third parties?We do not sell, license or share the personal information we collect with other businesses or third parties for monetary or other valuable consideration. We may share personal information in the following situations.Third Parties and Service ProvidersWe sometimes use third-parties or our service providers to act on our behalf, for example to help us fulfill your orders/reservations, process payments, enhance and personalize your experience with us, or to deliver our advertisements. Our service providers may receive your name and contact information, payment information, photos and other content you upload to our Sites and Apps, information about purchases you have made, cookies and other device identifiers, IP address and website browsing and interaction activity. These service providers are only allowed to use your information in connection with the specific service they provide on our behalf.Partners and AffiliatesWe share your information for purposes described in this Policy.Law Enforcement, Mergers and Other SituationsWe may be required to share your personal information in other, limited circumstances. For example, we may be required to share certain information to respond to a subpoena or similar judicial process, to comply with state, federal or local laws, to protect the security or integrity of our databases or website, to take precautions against liability, in the event of a corporate reorganization or, to the extent required by law, to provide information to law enforcement agencies. Additionally, your information may be transferred to another organization if, for example, we transfer the ownership or operation because we have merged with or have been acquired by another organization, or if we liquidate our assets. In those cases, the new company’s use of your information will still be subject to this Policy and the privacy preferences you have expressed to us.What options do you have to limit our collection and use of your personal information?You have choices about how your information is collected and used.  You can notify us of your preferences when you create an account with us, and if you would like to review, correct or delete your account information on our Sites and Apps, you can do so by contacting us directly. There may be times when we are unable to fulfill your request – for example, if providing access to your personal information would reveal confidential commercial or proprietary information or personal information about someone else (and we cannot separate your data), if we are prohibited by law from disclosing the information, or if we have a legal obligation to retain certain data. We may require additional personal information from you for the purposes of verifying your identity and rights.Opting out of Marketing CommunicationsIf you no longer want to receive marketing communications from us, you can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages you receive, by changing your marketing preferences through our subscription center, or by contacting us through the Contact Us page. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the services we provide, such as service announcements and administrative messages (for example, communications related to an upcoming reservation, pending order, an unresolved customer service issue, or a policy update). We do not offer you the ability to opt-out of receiving those communications.Cookie OptionsIf you do not want our Sites and Apps to collect information using Cookies, you can change your web browser settings to reject Cookies from the site or to alert you before a cookie is placed on your computer. Each browser is different, so you should check your browser’s “Help” menu to learn how to change your cookie preferences. Please note that cookie-based opt-outs only apply to the specific computer and browser on which the opt-out cookie is applied. If you accept a cookie, you can delete it at any time through your web browser. If you choose not to accept Cookies, though, you will not be able to enjoy all the features available to our registered users.The Network Advertising Alliance (“NAI”) and the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) offer opt-out tools to help you manage your choices for participating companies that use Cookies for Interest-Based Advertising and cross-app advertising. For more information about these tools, please visit: NAI Opt-Out Page and DAA Opt-Out Page. You can also opt out of Google cookies by installing Google Analytics’ opt-out browser add-on https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout, and/or the Google Advertising Cookie out-out browser add-on. “Do Not Track” is a preference you can set in your web browser to let the sites you visit know that you do not want them collecting information about you. Our sites do not currently respond to “Do Not Track” settings.How do we keep your information secure?Although no website, application, database or system is completely secure or “hacker proof,” we have safeguards in place to protect against unauthorized access and disclosures of the personal information we control, including technical, physical and administrative safeguards and security measures. Despite these measures, however, we cannot guarantee that our information security safeguards will never be compromised. If a breach is identified, Pinehurst will notify you in a timely manner.Our Sites and Apps may be linked on other websites or may contain links to other websites. Our Privacy Policy only applies to our Sites and Apps, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices, security standards, or content of other sites. You should check the privacy policies of those sites before providing your personal information to them. See our Terms of Use for additional information.How do we make updates to this policy?As we implement new technology and introduce new services or otherwise change our privacy practices, or in response to changes in applicable laws or regulations, we may modify this Policy and provide notice to you by posting updates on this page. Please check back periodically to view any updates. Changes to our Policy will become effective when posted.  If we change this Privacy Policy in a material way, we will endeavor to promptly notify our customers.  Your continued use of our websites, mobile applications and/or other services following such notice acknowledges your acceptance of such updated terms.How can you contact us with questions about your privacy or this Policy?For further information regarding this website privacy statement or related Pinehurst Resort’s policies and procedures, please contact: privacy@Pinehurst.com.Supplemental Notice to California ResidentsEffective Date: January 1, 2020If you are a California resident, California law may apply to how we collect and use your personal information, and what rights you have in some circumstances. The following terms supplement our Privacy Policy and explain the rights of California residents.For information about what categories of personal information we may collect from our customers, the sources of that information, the purposes for collecting and using that information, and what types of third party service providers we may share that information with, please see our section titled What personal information do we collect? How do we use that information?California residents and/or their authorized agents have the following rights:The right to request information about personal information that we have collected about that customer in the 12 months preceding the customer’s request (including the categories of information collected, the source of that information, the business purpose of that collection and the specific pieces of personal information collected about that particular customer);The right to request information about personal information that we have disclosed for a business purpose or sold to third parties in the 12 months preceding the customer’s request (including the categories of information disclosed, if any, for a business purpose or sold to third parties, and for each category of personal information identified, the categories of third parties to whom the information was disclosed or sold);The right to opt-out of sale of personal informationThe right to receive requested information in a readily usable format if provided electronically;The right to request that we delete any personal information about the consumer that we have collected (although we may be entitled to retain some information for certain purposes); andThe right to freely exercise your rights without being denied goods or services.We cannot respond to your request to access or delete information unless we are able to both verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the personal information relates to you and/or your household. We will attempt to verify your request by asking you to provide identifying information that we will match to information in our files. We will only use information you provide in your request for verifying your identity or authority to make the request. You can also designate an authorized agent to make a request on your behalf. Your agent will need to provide a Power of Attorney authorizing the agent to act on your behalf, or will need to complete the same verification procedures that would be required for a request submitted by you directly, and provide information that allows us to verify your authorization.We may deny deletion requests in whole or in part as permitted or required by applicable law. We do not charge a different price or rate or provide a different level or quality of goods or services based on your exercising your CCPA rights. We do not sell personal information.If you are a California resident under the age of 18, and a registered user of any site where this policy is posted, you may request and obtain removal of content or information. To make such a request, please send an email with the subject line “California Minor Content Removal Request” to privacy@pinehurst.com.To ask questions, express concerns about the privacy policy and practices, get more information or exercise your rights under California law with respect to Pinehurst Resort, please contact us as follows and provide your first name, last name and email address:Email privacy@pinehurst.comPhone: (866) 311-9730CloseRequest Trip InfoClose OverlayPlan Your StayTell us more about your trip in 3 easy steps, and we’ll help you design the your perfect Pinehurst experience.Thank you foryour reservation inquiry!We will be in touch within 24 hours to assist with your reservation.Tell us more about your trip in 3 easy steps, and we’ll help you design your perfect Pinehurst experience.Thank you for your reservation inquiry. We will be in touch within 24 hours to assist with your reservation. Step 1 Step 2 Step 3
Arrival *
Departure *What courses are you interested in playing?
Course No. 1
Course No. 2
Course No. 3
Course No. 4
Course No. 5
Course No. 6
Course No. 7
Course No. 8
Course No. 9 Continue Reason for Your StayGolf TripSpa TripPleasure / VacationOther
Reason for Your Stay Adults in your group12345678910
Adults in your group Children in your group012345678910
Children in your group Preferred accommodationNo PreferenceThe Carolina HotelThe Carolina VillasThe Holly InnThe Manor Inn
Preferred accommodation Number of golfers in party12345678910
Number of golfers in party Number of rounds12345
Number of rounds Interested In Spa Service?YesNoMaybe
Number of rounds Continue
First Name*
Last Name*
Email Address*
Phone Number*
Zip/Postal Code*
Country Start PlanningGet Info Call UsPinehurst Resort uses cookies to improve your experience on our site, analyze web traffic and serve targeted advertisements. By continuing to use our site, you accept our use of cookies. View our privacy & cookie policy here. Accept
